// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What punctuation ends most lines of C code?",
    answer: ";",
    options: [
      ".",
      ";",
      ":",
      "?"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "In a C program, the first statement that will be executed is:",
    answer: "The first executable statement of the main() function.",
    options: [
      "The first executable statement of the program.",
      "The first executable statement of the main() function.",
      "The first executable statement after the comment /*start here*/",
      "The first executable statement of the end function."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "How would you insert pre-written code into a current program?",
    answer: "#include",
    options: [
      "#read",
      "#get",
      "#include",
      "#pre"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who is known as the founder of C language?",
    answer: "Dennis Ritchie",
    options: [
      "Dennis Ritchie",
      "James Gosling",
      "Martin Richard",
      "David Richard"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What function is used to print something on console?",
    answer: "printf()",
    options: [
      "printf()",
      "scanf()",
      "main()",
      "getch()"
    ]
  },
  
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which symbol is used to make comments in C?",
    answer: "//",
    options: [
      "#",
      "//",
      "!!",
      "**"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following are NOT relational operators?",
    answer: "==",
    options: [
      "<",
      ">",
      "==",
      "<="
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which mathematical operators are in the correct order?",
    answer: "Division, Multiplication, Modulus",
    options: [
      "Addition, Division, Modulus ",
      "Division, Multiplication, Modulus",
      "Modulus, Division, Multiplication",
      "Modulus, Addition, Division"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "In which standard library file is the function printf() located?",
    answer: "stdio.h",
    options: [
      "stdlib.h",
      "stdio.h",
      "stdout.h",
      "stdoutput.h"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which function is used to read the input from console?",
    answer: "scanf()",
    options: [
      "clrscr()",
      "getchar()",
      "scanf()",
      "printf()"
    ]
  },
];